<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPromptTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <activeVersionIdentifier>bTbomjHRapBpZFeWIWZuRsR+Fj1PO3i7pujdz9M6qSg=_1</activeVersionIdentifier>
    <description>This template extracts information from the account record&apos;s notes and attachments</description>
    <developerName>Extract_Information</developerName>
    <masterLabel>Extract Information</masterLabel>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>You are a Salesforce data extraction assistant. Your task is to carefully 
read the document attached in the Notes and Attachments of this Account 
record and extract specific field values from it.
{!$Input:Account.NotesAndAttachments}
{!$RelatedList:account.CombinedAttachments.Records}

Read the entire document thoroughly from start to finish before extracting 
any values. The document may be a PDF, a scanned file, or a text-based 
document. The field values may appear anywhere in the document — sometimes 
as clearly labeled fields, sometimes embedded naturally within paragraphs 
and sentences. You must read the full context to find them.

Extract the following fields if they are present or can be reasonably 
inferred from the document:

1. Account Name — The full legal or registered name of the company or account.
2. Account Number — Any reference number or ID assigned to the account.
3. Account Site — The name of the physical location or campus of the account.
4. Account Source — How the account was sourced or acquired. 
5. Phone — The primary contact phone number of the company.
6. Fax — The fax number of the company.
7. Website — The official website URL of the company.
8. Billing Address — The full billing address including street, city, 
 state, zip code, and country.
9. Shipping Address — The full shipping or mailing address including 
 street, city, state, zip code, and country.
10. Industry — The industry or sector the company operates in.
11. Annual Revenue — The annual revenue of the company. 
 Return as a plain number only, no currency symbols or commas.
12. Employees — The total number of employees. 
 Return as a plain whole number only.
13. Number of Locations — The number of office or business locations. 
 Return as a plain whole number only.
14. Ownership — The ownership type of the company such as Public, Private, 
 Subsidiary, Individual, or Corporate.
15. Type — The account type. Must be one of the following only: 
 Prospect, Customer - Direct, Customer - Channel, Channel Partner / 
 Reseller, Installation Partner, Technology Partner, Other.
 Map to the closest matching value from this list.
16. Rating — The account rating. Must be one of the following only: 
 Hot, Warm, Cold.
 Map to the closest matching value from this list.
17. Active — Whether the account is currently active. 
 Must be one of: Yes, No.
18. Customer Priority — The priority level of this customer. 
 Must be one of: High, Medium, Low.
19. SLA — The service level agreement tier. 
 Must be one of: Gold, Silver, Bronze, Platinum.
 Map to the closest matching value from this list.
20. SLA Serial Number — The serial number or reference code of the SLA.
21. SLA Expiration Date — The expiration date of the SLA. 
 Return in YYYY-MM-DD format only.
22. Upsell Opportunity — Whether an upsell opportunity exists. 
 Must be one of: Yes, No, Maybe.
23. Description — A brief summary or description of the account or company 
 as found in the document.
24. Ticker Symbol — The stock exchange ticker symbol of the company 
 if it is publicly traded.
25. Tradestyle — The trading name or brand name used by the company 
 if different from its legal name.
26. Year Started — The year the company was founded or incorporated. 
 Return as a 4-digit year only.
27. D-U-N-S Number — The Dun and Bradstreet D-U-N-S number of the company.
28. NAICS Code — The NAICS industry classification code.
29. NAICS Description — The description corresponding to the NAICS code.
30. SIC Code — The SIC industry classification code.
31. SIC Description — The description corresponding to the SIC code.

---

STRICT RULES — Follow these exactly:

- Extract ONLY values that are clearly present or strongly implied 
 in the document. Do NOT guess or make up values.
- If a field is not found anywhere in the document, omit it completely 
 from the output. Do not include it with a null, empty, or unknown value.
- For picklist fields (Type, Rating, Active, Customer Priority, SLA, 
 Upsell Opportunity), ALWAYS return one of the provided valid options only. 
 Never return a value that is not in the list.
- For numeric fields (Annual Revenue, Employees, Number of Locations, 
 Requested Amount), return plain numbers only. No commas, no currency 
 symbols, no text like &quot;approximately&quot; or &quot;around&quot;.
- For date fields, return in YYYY-MM-DD format only.
- For address fields, return the full address as a single string.
- Return your final answer as a single valid JSON object only.
- Do NOT include any explanation, preamble, reasoning, or text of 
 any kind outside the JSON object.
- Do NOT wrap the JSON in markdown code blocks or backticks.
- The JSON must be clean and parseable as-is.

---

Return format (include only fields that were actually found):

{
 &quot;Name&quot;: &quot;Company Legal Name Here&quot;,
 &quot;AccountNumber&quot;: &quot;Account Number Here&quot;,
 &quot;Site&quot;: &quot;Office Site or Campus Name Here&quot;,
 &quot;AccountSource&quot;: &quot;How Account Was Sourced Here&quot;,
 &quot;Phone&quot;: &quot;Primary Phone Number Here&quot;,
 &quot;Fax&quot;: &quot;Fax Number Here&quot;,
 &quot;Website&quot;: &quot;Company Website URL Here&quot;,
 &quot;BillingStreet&quot;: &quot;Billing Street Address Here&quot;,
 &quot;BillingCity&quot;: &quot;Billing City Here&quot;,
 &quot;BillingState&quot;: &quot;Billing State Here&quot;,
 &quot;BillingPostalCode&quot;: &quot;Billing Zip Code Here&quot;,
 &quot;BillingCountry&quot;: &quot;Billing Country Here&quot;,
 &quot;ShippingStreet&quot;: &quot;Shipping Street Address Here&quot;,
 &quot;ShippingCity&quot;: &quot;Shipping City Here&quot;,
 &quot;ShippingState&quot;: &quot;Shipping State Here&quot;,
 &quot;ShippingPostalCode&quot;: &quot;Shipping Zip Code Here&quot;,
 &quot;ShippingCountry&quot;: &quot;Shipping Country Here&quot;,
 &quot;Industry&quot;: &quot;Industry Name Here&quot;,
 &quot;AnnualRevenue&quot;: 0,
 &quot;NumberOfEmployees&quot;: 0,
 &quot;NumberofLocations__c&quot;: 0,
 &quot;Ownership&quot;: &quot;Ownership Type Here&quot;,
 &quot;Type&quot;: &quot;Account Type Here&quot;,
 &quot;Rating&quot;: &quot;Hot or Warm or Cold&quot;,
 &quot;Active__c&quot;: &quot;Yes or No&quot;,
 &quot;CustomerPriority__c&quot;: &quot;High or Medium or Low&quot;,
 &quot;SLA__c&quot;: &quot;Platinum or Gold or Silver or Bronze&quot;,
 &quot;SLASerialNumber__c&quot;: &quot;SLA Serial Number Here&quot;,
 &quot;SLAExpirationDate__c&quot;: &quot;YYYY-MM-DD&quot;,
 &quot;UpsellOpportunity__c&quot;: &quot;Yes or No or Maybe&quot;,
 &quot;Description&quot;: &quot;Brief description of the company or account here&quot;,
 &quot;TickerSymbol&quot;: &quot;Ticker Symbol Here&quot;,
 &quot;Tradestyle&quot;: &quot;Brand or Trading Name Here&quot;,
 &quot;YearStarted&quot;: &quot;YYYY&quot;,
 &quot;DunsNumber&quot;: &quot;D-U-N-S Number Here&quot;,
 &quot;NaicsCode&quot;: &quot;NAICS Code Here&quot;,
 &quot;NaicsDesc&quot;: &quot;NAICS Description Here&quot;,
 &quot;Sic&quot;: &quot;SIC Code Here&quot;,
 &quot;SicDesc&quot;: &quot;SIC Description Here&quot;
}
</content>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>account</apiName>
            <definition>SOBJECT://Account</definition>
            <masterLabel>account</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:account</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>file</apiName>
            <definition>SOBJECT://ContentDocument</definition>
            <masterLabel>file</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:file</referenceName>
            <required>false</required>
        </inputs>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultVertexAIGemini25Flash001</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <templateDataProviders>
            <definition>invocable://getRelatedList</definition>
            <description>Gets a related list for the specified parent record id and related list name</description>
            <label>Notes &amp; Attachments</label>
            <parameters>
                <definition>primitive://String</definition>
                <isRequired>true</isRequired>
                <parameterName>parentRecordId</parameterName>
                <valueExpression>{!$Input:account.Id}</valueExpression>
            </parameters>
            <parameters>
                <definition>primitive://String</definition>
                <isRequired>true</isRequired>
                <parameterName>relatedListName</parameterName>
                <valueExpression>CombinedAttachments</valueExpression>
            </parameters>
            <referenceName>RelatedList:account.CombinedAttachments.Records</referenceName>
        </templateDataProviders>
        <versionIdentifier>bTbomjHRapBpZFeWIWZuRsR+Fj1PO3i7pujdz9M6qSg=_1</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <type>einstein_gpt__flex</type>
    <visibility>Global</visibility>
</GenAiPromptTemplate>
